Give me four days
and I can arrange the flight.
So, where are we going?
I'm thinking maybe Thailand or Vietnam,
but it might be easier for you in Thailand
because you know people there.
Yeah.
I'll go through and make the arrangements.
I'd also recommend
some S-class bloodhounds.
If you have three,
then that should get the job done.
That is
if you're trying
to kidnap Kim Gun-woo's mother.
How much?
300 million each. So 900 million.
You're wanted and we don't have much time.
We have to do this the right way.
It's a
necessary investment.
S-class is special,
I promise you with my life,
because they'll do the job right.
Get us two, would ya? You're number three.
I understand.
Who's that?
It's just my mother.
Then take it.
-Hey.
-Where are you right now?
-Why?
-Min-a got hit by a car.
What? How bad is it?
-Where are you?
-The ER at Seonkuk University Medical.
-Hurry up and get here.
-Got it.
My daughter was hit by a car.
They're at the hospital.
Go then.
Show me your ID, please.
Just a second.
-And the name of the patient?
-Yun Min-a.
Okay, come on in.
Room's around the corner and to the left.
Min-a.
Oh, Dad!
I need you all in position.
Are you okay?
Huh?
Listen to me.
Please stop doing this.
Tae-geom. Tae-geom!
That's enough. Hey, stop!
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Put the guns down.
-Put the guns down.
-Min-a.
Close your eyes and hold on tight.
It's all right. Put them down.
Hey! Put them down. It's okay.
It's okay.
Tae-geom, hey.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Let's just talk.
I promise, I'm really just here
to talk to you.
I also have a young daughter.
From one dad to another,
let's just talk about it.
Sir, what brings you in?
A guest sent by your uncle
has arrived, sir.
I want to thank you for coming here.
Nice to meet you. I'm Choi Sin-hyeong.
Hmm. I know the name's a bit unusual.
It's a code name I go by.
BLOODHOUNDS 2
If they were to bring you in, you'd get
a life sentence or the death penalty.
If you help us, I'll do my very best
to get you the life sentence.
And what would be the point of that?
If you're sentenced to death, you won't
be able to have visitors or seek parole.
But with a life sentence,
it could be possible to get parole,
assuming that you're good.
Yun Tae-geom, sir.
I mean, bro.
Didn't you start working under
Im Baek-jeong to provide for your family?
Well, then, you should do
whatever it takes
so you can live
to protect your mother and daughter.
Your family? They're never gonna give up
on you, no matter how much you screw up.
And your mother?
That woman would do almost anything
to save her child, even if it kills her.
You know that. And your daughter?
Hey, man, your daughter, I bet she'd wait
her whole fucking life just to see you.
But man, "the point?"
You can't see the point? Is that it, huh?
Is that the type of dad that they need?
Fine, then.
Be that guy.
Tae-geom, please.
It's not over until it's over.
We could still do more for each other.
I'm sure of it.
So, how about you join us?
Keep my family safe from Im Baek-jeong.
I promise you that.
What do you want me to say?
Well, first, where is Im Baek-jeong?
He's on the move,
aboard his yacht on the Han River.
If I contact him,
he'll tell me the pickup point.
The yacht could be docking
at one of three positions.
He's a smart guy.
How about we raid them tonight?
If by chance we fail to arrest him,
won't Tae-geom be in danger?
How about we maintain his cover
and wait for the right opportunity?
We could. You're right.
But, um, how did he know
we would be raiding the Entra Hotel?
I believe he was informed by an employee.
Lots of people in his circle, then?
Yes.
Who's organizing all this for him?
That's what I need from you.
Could it… could it be a cop?
There's a guy called Lee Dong-hyeon.
He was an NIS agent.
Lee Man-bae, right?
His actual name is Lee Dong-hyeon.
Is he the one
who gave the order to kill Gi-na?
Yes.
So, who in the police force
does he control?
I'm not sure yet.
I know for sure there was more than one.
I could hear that much
from his phone call.
He's a meticulous man.
Then it's possible he could have heard
about the wanted alert.
Lee Dong-hyeon's looking
for a private plane.
I'll bet you he's going to Thailand.
He couldn't do that with a warrant though.
He's the kind of man
that would make it happen.
Our goal
is to capture Kim Gun-woo's mother
and take her to Thailand.
Im Baek-jeong wants
to fight Kim Gun-woo again.
So he plans to kidnap his mother
to lure him in.
For ransom money?
It seems that Baek-jeong
has a more personal reason.
I think he believes he lost to Kim Gun-woo
in that previous fight they had.
Because viewers all over the world
rooted for Kim Gun-woo to win.
So while everyone's watching,
Kim Gun-woo's going to be killed.
Gun-woo's gonna what?
There are a few ways to fight in the IKFC.
One of those is a death match.
They fight until one of them dies.
That's the fight
that makes the most money.
So kidnapping Gun-woo's mother.
How's he doing it?
Dong-hyeon is paying S-class bloodhounds.
What's that?
They're professional killers for hire.
The S-class means that Dong-hyeon's people
are as deadly as they could be.
So then, do you think he also knows
where Gun-woo's mother is staying?
I don't have a clue.
It wasn't ever mentioned?
No.
PRESIDENT
Im Baek-jeong?
Let's tell him that Min-a hurt her head
and she's waiting for a scan right now.
Sir.
How is she?
She hit her head pretty bad on the ground.
She's gonna get a CT scan.
-Wrap it up and get back.
-Okay.
Tae-geom.
-Kim Jin-su, please come in.
-Okay.
The wound is healing well,
so you don't have anything to worry about.
I appreciate it.
How's your shoulder?
Um, it hurts a little.
Could I see it?
Do you need painkillers?
I'll be okay.
All right, then.
Min-beom.
How's it going?
This room is so small.
You want me to upgrade you?
Oh, no, this room's already
too much for me, but thanks anyway.
I'm going to the hospital
to visit Gang-yong.
-Could you let me come?
-No, you shouldn't.
I'll talk to him and call you.
Just rest up.
Okay.
Seul-gi, have you thought
about your code name?
I haven't thought of anything yet.
You know, your look is delicate,
so it's important
that you pick a strong name.
Something like… Jung Hwa-gi.
Jung Hwa-gi?
-You don't like it?
-It'd be an honor.
I'm just joking.
What kind of name is Hwa-gi?
How about Kang Ryeok-han?
Ryeok-han?
Mm.
Incredible.
I'm good at making code names.
Hello?
-The meeting's about to start.
-All right.
HONG MIN-BEOM
PRESIDENT OF IIL GROUP
We'll have two chances.
When they come to kidnap Gun-woo's mother.
And when they get off the yacht
to flee abroad.
Is this person trustworthy?
Yun Tae-geom?
-We'd say he's worthy of your trust.
-Hmm. I agree with that.
How about Gun-woo's mother? Is she safe?
Well, we did talk about that too.
Where she's at now is the safest.
Woo-jin and Woo-jeong
will stay at the hotel
and they have guards to keep her safe.
So if they're after his mother,
does Gun-woo know?
He doesn't know. Gun-woo wouldn't
think twice about leaving the hospital.
Probably, yeah.
I'd like it if he could just focus
on his recovery.
I believe we can ensure
his mother's safety.
It'll be more dangerous
if Gun-woo fights in his current state.
So…
what do we do once we catch 'em?
Hmm?
Punish them to the fullest legal extent.
That doesn't feel like enough.
I'm still anxious
with Kim Myeong-gil behind bars.
We need something… more.
So then how do you wanna deal with it?
Could you excuse us?
No, Gwang-mu, it's okay.
It's okay. Just say it.
I want him dead.
My uncle
assigned some agents to me.
What kind of agents?
Black ops.
This issue is ours. There's
no reason for the NIS to get involved.
-Well, can you kill these guys?
-Min-beom.
We have to… let them
spend the rest of their lives in jail,
reflecting on what they've done,
and return all that stolen wealth
back to society.
Do you understand?
I need to see these stupid fucks gone.
You know that isn't justice.
I have people.
Min-beom, we need to be
on the same page about this.
Then I'll do it my way.
You should know, my dad won bronze
at the Barcelona Olympics,
so I asked him if he happened
to know of a guy named Im Baek-jeong.
Apparently, Im Baek-jeong
was a student to his friend.
Whoa.
He remembered him because he said he was
ambidextrous and had a really good hook.
According to my father, everyone
expected him to become a world champion,
but he's a piece of shit, I guess,
and he totally ruined it for himself.
Mm.
So then, I asked him some more about it
to see if he might be in touch
with the coach who taught Im Baek-jeong.
I mean a coach is the person who would
know almost anything about his boxer.
Go-to moves, weaknesses, all his steps.
That's right. I bet that you'd know
all of my weaknesses.
I, um, watched the video of you fighting
Im Baek-jeong over and over again.
I was thinking about
what kind of advice I could give you
to help you beat him in a fight, and…
I don't think I'm a good enough coach.
I'm at a loss for answers.
I promise it's not your coaching.
I don't know if I've seen an ambidextrous
fighter that could change up his stance.
I just couldn't keep up with him.
Well, his left jab
looked super strong and heavy.
It was. Also, that right hand's fast.
Honestly, I can't really remember
how I fought.
Yeah, so, Gun-woo, how about
we go and get you trained by that coach?
You know, the one
who taught Im Baek-jeong?
This coach could know
the method that might beat Im Baek-jeong.
-Good idea.
-Is it?
I want to win.
Argh. Ow.
-I'm okay, I'm okay.
-What are you doing?
Huh?
-There's food.
-Oh.
-Eat slowly.
-Hmm.
Here.
I don't want you guys to be
getting into something dangerous.
It just breaks my heart
when you guys get hurt.
Don't worry too much, Mom.
How can I not worry
when you're hurt like that?
I'll take better care of him, Mom.
Go ahead.
-Is there any kimchi?
-Just eat your food.
Mm.
Let's grab those kimchi noodles
from the convenience store afterwards.
-Pretty much the same thing.
-Let's do that.
Damn, this egg tastes better cold.
I used the entire carton of eggs.
Don't eat too fast.
-Hmm.
-Here.
We are currently divided into two teams
that are working in two shifts.
As of now, both Team A and Team B will be
staying on the 16th floor of the hotel.
If we encounter a situation,
both teams can respond together.
So then, how many people is that?
There are a total of 12 personnel.
Uh, you can vouch for their skills?
Yes, you don't have to worry.
Ah.
Uh, when…
When we take down Im Baek-jeong,
will the Major Crimes Unit be enough?
No, not at all.
Should I call the mobile unit?
Uh, that's not what I meant.
We still don't know who took the money
from Im Baek-jeong, and it's worrying.
Mr. Min, would you like me
to get some Marines?
It wouldn't work.
Oh, yeah.
What about the Green Pine Tree Club?
Oh.
Yoon Han-gu, the sergeant?
Is Han-gu in Suwon currently?
Yeah. Baek-jeong's money
shouldn't have gone out that far so…
Okay, I'll reach out to him.
Hey.
Hey, Diego.
You sure know how to pick a place to meet.
Happy birthday, Captain.
I asked for US dollars.
I'm sorry. I didn't have enough time.
I'm gonna need an extra 10%
when we get to Bangkok.
Yeah, fine.
Wednesday, 3 a.m.
See you in Cheongju.
Yeah. Okay.
Understood.
Let's get the stitches removed
tomorrow at 10:00.
I'll handle it, sir.
Two nights from now,
Gun-woo's mother will go to the airport.
Say goodbye to your daughter.
It's gonna be a while.
Yes.
Han-gu, thanks a lot.
Anything for family.
This is the Violent Crimes Unit.
-Hi.
-He's our head detective.
-Thank you for coming.
-Nice to meet you.
The owner of the veterinary clinic,
Moon Dong-jo,
has served three prison terms for
manufacturing and distributing narcotics.
He's been practicing illegally
since his license was revoked in 2022.
Here are photos from the site.
Now, let me explain the mission.
Team 1 will wait
at the back door of the clinic,
Team 2 at the restaurant,
and Team 3 at the salon.
Headquarters will give a signal to move in
once the suspect enters the clinic.
Suspects may try to escape
through the back door of the clinic.
Team 1, be as vigilant as possible.
Now, some key info.
Trust only the people in this room.
If you see any unexpected backup,
be on your guard.
It's possible there are cops
who've been bought.
Let's work together and show them all
what great cops are really made of.
Yes, sir!
Oh shit. Motherfucker.
MOON DONG-JO VETERINARY CLINIC
Team 1, you're in position, right?
Team 1, in position.
Team 2?
Team 2, copy.
Team 3?
All clear.
Vehicle approaching. Stand by, stand by.
Action!
-Let's go.
-Go, go, go!
-Freeze! Don't move!
-Get him!
Police!
-Get his ass!
-Come out!
Shit.
Im Baek-jeong.
Put your hands in the air.
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
You fucking bastard!
Son of a bitch!
Stay still!
Shoot his ass!
Get him!
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything that you say
can and will be used against you.
Now, get up!
Don't fucking move.
Stay right there.
I'm Min Gang-yong.
I'm gonna make sure that you rot in jail.
Yes!
Yeah!
What are you doing?
Tell me what're you doing!
Why should I go on doing this?
How much you want, huh?
Five Bitcoins. Got it?
-You want 500 million won for this?
-Yeah.
Shit!
I sent it.
Thank you for the payment.
BLOODHOUNDS : SEOUL
Son of a bitch.
Oh, just hit it.
STAREX FROM CLINIC TO POLICE
EXTRACTION, 200 MIL
Let's go make some money.
It's 200 million. Hurry up!
Let's fucking go!
FROM MOON DONG-JO VETERINARY CLINIC
STAREX VAN TO NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
SAVE MY COLLEAGUES, 200 MIL
MOON DONG-JO VETERINARY CLINIC
What's that?
What's going on?
Ah, shit!
Fucking hell.
Hey, get out of the fucking way!
Whoa, shit!
-What now?
-Let's just get out of here.
Requesting backup here at Jinho Bridge.
Car accident. Car accident.
Shit. Shit.
Ah!
-Come on! Come on!
-Open it! Get the fucking door! Come on!
-Yeah!
-Open the fucking door! Get out!
Come on. Get in there. Let's go!
Oh shit.
Come here!
Agh!
Stay out of it!
Son of a bitch!
Let go, you little bitch!
Motherfucker!
Agh!
Agh! Agh!
Get me out of these. I can help you.
Han-gu, help him.
Get Baek-jeong.
-Round 'em up!
-Get up!
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
Don't move.
Stay still, you bitch.
Shit.
Fuck you, you little…
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Dumb motherfucker!
Die, you dumb motherfucker!
Hey!
Come on.
Yes.
Open it.
Agh!
I… will make sure your daughter dies.
SWAG S
Yes?
Grab Gun-woo's mother.
Yes.
Gun-woo's mother's room key.
I sent it.
Please go easy on Ji-uk.
Don't worry about him.
I'm all better now. I'm okay.
NO INTERNET ACCESS
Get ready.
Stay in formation.
Gyeong-nam.
Call the police.
And don't come out, no matter what.
-Get up.
-Yeah!
Dumb shit.
Oh!
Oh, yeah, we're here
at the Yeongdeungpo Marriott Hotel.
Whoo!
Don't do it, Woo-jin.
Mom.
Come on!
Would you stop hitting him?
Please stop it.
I'll just go with you.
I'm begging you. I'll go with you.
Woo-jin.
Not right now.
Please listen to me.
No, please.
You can't go. Mom, I'll go instead.
Woo-jin…
…I'm going to be okay.
Don't follow me.
No!
Mom!
Mom, wait!
Mom! I'll go. Mom!
No, Mom!